[{"answer": "That's a really good question.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Why aren't you as a productive two superstars just lying on some sun lounger in a bikini spending daddy's money being a brat?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I don't know.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Where do you get this desire to scare people?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, you have to have really good characters because if you don't have somebody that you really want to spend time with, it might be -- it's going to be a workman like sort of book.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "When you were trying to analyze the best way to do it -- you're one of the best people to ask -- what is it?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "I was very disturbed.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "What conclusions did you draw after that about the death penalty?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "ORNWELL: I do.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Is that how you feel?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "I draw the line like I was saying a minute ago, like if someone said, do you want to watch an execution for research purposes, I would say no.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Where do you draw the line as a writer?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Well, the first three books I wrote they should have rejected, they were really awful.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "How do you feel about the people that rejected you?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I think I am a Democrat now.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "And are you a Democrat?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "I think we should give him another chance.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Is President Obama that person?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I've not only heard about that, I went -- looked at the autopsy report.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "If you're a crime writer of your renown, do you read that kind of thing in the paper and get, you know, pretty excited?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Did you really?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "That it was a really well done autopsy and there is no evidence whatsoever that she was a victim of foul play.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "And what was your conclusion?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Sure, you get some.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Do you have crazies coming after you?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "She's attached to it and we're hoping to begin filming next year.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "I think it's going to be way cool, lots of fun.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "How cool is that?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "That's what you want to hear, isn't it?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I think about it every day, because I still get inspiration from cases I had back then, clients I knew, people I knew back 20, 30 years ago.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Do you ever do that?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "No, it was very gradual.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Was there a wakeup moment, a utopia moment when you went, whoa?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Well, unfortunately, Mitch --", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "CDEERE: Reveal privileged information that violates attorney- client confidences, get me disbarred then testify in open court against the mafia?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "It's certainly not true in real life.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "But that's not true in real life, is it?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Well, if not for DNA, there would be no Innocence Project.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What do you make of that debate, given the way that the law has changed due to technology in many ways?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, personally, yes, I'm opposed to the death penalty, very much opposed to it for a lot of reasons, moral reasons but also questions of fairness, how it's implemented.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Do you think it's time just to move on?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Didn't really follow that closely.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "What did you think of that?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "You know, I hate to pass judgment.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Do you think the right verdict was reached in that case?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Dream come true.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "The Muppets, Miss Piggy, dream come true?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Let's have a little look at this, because this is the stuff of dreams.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Because how is it going to get any better than this?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Yeah, I wanted to talk to you about that.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Did you fund a celebrity?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Best acting I've ever done in my life.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "How could do you that?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "That's a really good question.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Why aren't you, as a productive of two superstars, just lying on some sun lounger in a bikini, spending daddy's money, being a brat?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Michael Jackson, Ray Charles.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Biggest names that walked through that door?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "It was a childish prank, yeah.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Didn't you go in a car with Michael Jackson once and spray gun complete strangers with a water pistol?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "You actually did that?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "He did.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "That guy just knew how to do it, didn't he?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Maybe I don't know.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "That would have been that, right?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the star part of it was never interesting to me.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "But did you have any kind of gut feeling you wanted to be like them, be a star?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "So sweet.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "That is so sweet, isn't it?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "That's funny.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "What does he think your biggest talent is?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Home run, isn't it?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "And nourishing the soul.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "You want to come touch the turtle?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "Hey, did you maybe tell people that I diagnosed that guy with mumps based on his porn photo?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Um --", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "What's going on?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "But who would be the perfect guy be?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "That's a good question.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Make you laugh or laugh at your jokes?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Love and romance?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "You know, I've never won -- I was thinking about this, I have never won anything before as a performer.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "Is that -- is that the holy grail for you as a performer?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "I think he would go for the Grammy, because he really wants me to sing.", "docId": "111209pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "If I said to your father, right, I can award Rashida a Grammy for an album produced by you, Quincy Jones, or an Oscar, which one would he go for?", "qSentId": 710}]